scbt.com 2019-05-27

# Santa Cruz Biotechnology

Copyright ©, 2007-2018, Santa Cruz Biotechnology, Inc. All Rights Reserved. "Santa Cruz Biotechnology", and the Santa Cruz Biotechnology, Inc. logo, "Santa Cruz Animal Health", "San Juan Ranch", and the San Juan Ranch logo, “Supplement of Champions”, "UltraCruz", "ChemCruz", "ImmunoCruz", "ExactaCruz", "CrystalCruz" and "EZ Touch" are registered trademarks of Santa Cruz Biotechnology, Inc. All content contained in this website is property of Santa Cruz Biotechnology, Inc. and may be used only with the expressed written permission of Santa Cruz Biotechnology, Inc. All rights reserved. All other trademarks are the property of their respective owners.

Santa Cruz Biotechnology has established this privacy statement to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the personal information gathering, storage, and processing practices for our public websites (www.scahealth.com, www.scbt.com, www.santacruzbiotechnology.com, www.scbio.cn, dist.scbt.com, datasheets.scbt.com, and media.scbt.com) and internal systems.

Most web servers on the internet will automatically log your IP address when you visit a site. Our web servers do the same. We use the information to diagnose problems with our servers, and to administer our sites. Our web sites also use cookies to keep track of your shopping cart items and preferences, and we utilize third party services that send out transactional emails, and to collect reviews on our behalf. If you have previously opted-in to receive these e-mails, and longer want to be included, please update your preferences.

Our Web sites use a secure ordering system for customers to purchase products. If you provide your information to create an account or place an order, your information stored on our server to speed your future orders. Your contact information is utilized to confirm your order, to provide shipping notifications, and provided to the shipping carrier to deliver your order.

If you have requested that we send you routine fliers, email updates or catalogs, the information you furnish is used solely for that purpose. We also use your contact information to get in touch with you when necessary. It is not our policy to resell your information or distribute it to any other parties not working on our behalf. You may opt out of receiving future mailings at any time by updating your preferences.

We also collect information from you when you call, fax, e-mail, or submit product reviews. This information might be used to update your orders, to provide technical support, or to direct your requests to the appropriate resource. We typically only have information that you, or someone representing you, has directly provided. In some cases, your information may have been obtained from public sources, like published research papers.

This information is only accessible to our employees and contractors that have a legitimate need to access it. Because of the nature of our business, we do keep this information for as long as we are legally able to before anonymizing it. We do not collect information that is deemed sensitive, nor do we perform any profiling based on personal information.

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, to request a copy of your personal information, or to request to be forgotten, please feel free to contact:

Santa Cruz Biotechnology, Inc.  
10410 Finnell Street  
Dallas, Texas 75220 USA  
Email: [privacy@scbt.com](mailto:privacy@scbt.com)
